seoconsult.co.uk 2009-03-24

# SEO Consult, Privacy Policy

1\. SEO Consult is commmitted to ensuring that Your privacy is protected. This Privacy Policy explains how SEO Consult uses the information it collects about You.

2\. When You visit this Website You may be asked to provide information about yourself such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and details regarding your Sponsored Links accounts. SEO Consult may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring Website usage in order to help it develop this Website and its services ("Aggregate Data") for which this data will be held internally. This Aggregate Data will not include information that can be used to identify You. SEO Consult may also wish to provide you with information about special features of this Website or any services SEO Consult thinks may be of interest to you. If you would like to receive this information, please send an e-mail to support@clickconsult.co.uk.

3\. How SEO Consult protects your information. The internet is not a secure medium. However, SEO Consult has put in place various security procedures to protect Your Personal Data. SEO Consult's internal procedures cover the storage, access and disclosure of Your Personal Data.

4\. Updating your details. If any of the Personal Data that you have provided to SEO Consult changes, please let SEO Consult know the correct details by sending an e-mail to support@clickconsult.co.uk. Alternatively, you may contact SEO Consult using the details on the Contact page of this Website.

5\. Your consent by providing your Personal Data. You consent to the use of your Personal Data as set out in this Privacy Policy. The Data you submit to us is held internally according to the Data Protection Act 1998. If SEO Consult changes this Privacy Policy it will post the changes on this Website, and continued use of this Website will signify that you agree to any such changes.

6\. Cookies. By accessing this Website, you accept and agree that SEO Consult, its affiliated companies or its service providers may send cookies (small pieces of data placed on Your hard disk drive when you access a website or a certain part of a website) to Your computer or other access device in order to personalise Your visit to this Website and/or to learn more about your use or browsing habits while visiting this Website. The cookie may be a persistent or single session cookie.

## **Quick Enquiry Form**

* Required Field

## SEO for mobile phone websites

posted on: **2009/03/23** in **Mobile SEO**

What are the differences in search optimising for a mobile phone website versus a standard website And, do search engines treat a mobile search differently to a normal PC or desktop search If you have a normal website but want to create a mobile phone version of the sa...

## Monitoring Search Engine Optimisation Results

There are no cutting corners if youre aiming to achieve successful Search Engine Optimisation SEO results and no guarantees of 100 success either. Search Engine Optimisation techniques and skills are enhanced by having an understanding of your target market and your ...

## Ethical Search Engine Optimization

Ethical search engine optimization SEO techniques are crucial when planning an SEO campaign, or when generally maintaining the SEO of your website. Its referred to quite simply as a black hat or white hat approach to Search Engine Optimization though theres often grey...

Click Here for more SEO blogs
